Hi Doug. Oh, these are my potatoes in a second. Hey, I hope you're doing good too. Hello. Nice to see you
How's everyone doing? Hello, Doug is a member
Welcome
Everything's good
Hi VV, how are you? Hi everybody
Look they don't sell the they don't sell the swishers anymore
Those are my last ones I smoked I bought cigarettes
Hello to you
No, maybe look apology
Doug you're gonna say something sweet
Enjoy your dinner catch you later. Maybe take your time
Oh
Look people making I love when people make up my chat, but if you apologize very nice apology, that's how you do it guys
And a nice guy dog is
How's everyone doing?
Yeah, it's only all sometimes
It's just a weird place
That is a great place
Just think it's careful look with the wrong long streets
How's everyone doing today? Well, I went to the store picked up a
Couple drinks and I was driving on by the way and all of a sudden the bike stuff of the bikes broken
I still have my lock around the, at least I know, so I tested the lock, it works.
But wow, I'm so happy. I thought I was gonna be stuck. I was like, oh, what if it's stuck here?
I think the bike is stuck here. Someone actually said, nice bike. And so I know I have a nice bike.
But I mean, it's nice to see, it's my first compliment. I got it. I don't have a car. I might as well have a nice bike.
You know, so.
Very lucky. This is a nice bike. It's fast. Oh, wow. It was like 25 miles an hour
That's the need to throw the bikes and people
Well, it's locked so far. Yeah, I just leave it outside the I mean, I don't have to leave it outside the liquor store for a second
I mean, it's like my sister was like I need some kind of special alchemy. I don't know some special kind of lock
Fit
I don't know, I just got like a $10 on Amazon.
Yeah.
How's everyone doing tonight?
It's off to one person
Well, how's everyone doing?
Really should
Let's open with a song everyone like a song
instead of a number. I'll read it. This is Psalm 38.
A Psalm of David, a petition.
Lord, do not rebuke me in your anger, or discipline me in your wrath.
Your arrows have pierced me, and your hand has come down on me.
Because of your wrath, there is no health in my body. There is no stoutness in my bones.
Because of my sin, my guilt has overwhelmed me, like a burden too happy to bear.
My wounds fester and are loathsome because of my sinful folly.
I am bowed down and brought very low, all day long.
I go about mourning. My back is filled with searing pain.
There is no health in my body. I am feeble and utterly crushed.
I groan in anguish of heart.
All my longings lie open before you, Lord.
My sighing is not hidden from you.
My heart pounds, my strength fails me.
Even the light has gone from my eyes.
My friends companion devoid me because of my wounds.
My neighbors stay far away.
Those who want to unalive me set their traps.
Those who would harm me talk of my ruin.
All day long they schemes and lie.
I am like the death who cannot hear.
Like the mute who cannot speak I have become like ones who does not hear whose mouth can offer no reply
Lord I wait for you you will answer Lord my God for I said do not let them bloat or exalt themselves over me when my feet slip
For I am about to fall and my pain is ever with me. I confess my iniquity. I am troubled by my sin
Many have become my enemies without cause those who hate me without reason are numerous
Those who repay me with good my good with evil lodged accusations against me
Though I seek only to do what is good Lord do not forsake me
Do not be far from me my God come quickly to help me my Lord my Savior. Hi
Hi, Yon
That was interesting song it was interesting because it really talked a lot about
You know someone feeling
Some feeling breath and
Thinking for forgiveness and it's interesting poem that's in there interesting that I read that
But I hope that was good for everybody amen
Oh gosh, that's low batteries. I need to maybe it's Jesus out. Hold on
Hi
Hello
And that's something in the world like you know some people
Never feel like they can get forgiveness and so they can never get forgiveness like what
What motivation is there for them to change their behavior?
But I guess that can make it make things worse. I don't know
But you don't forgive other people
Because you know people are fallible people make mistakes everybody does
So
I'm very much on the side of forgiveness
I'm looking at some quotes I'm forgetting this.
Let's see.
forgive other people when they sin against you, your heavenly Father will also forgive you.
Bear with each other and forgive one another. If any of you has a grievance against someone,
forgive as the Lord forgave you. Do not judge and you will not be judged. Do not condemn and you
Hi, why is everyone so quiet?
How's everyone doing?
Talk to me.
I don't know.
I think, you know,
other people may be on right now.
So yeah, so,
my friend
is coming over again.
Unless you might be here any minute,
she's been helping me clean my house.
You're really cool
So she's she came and then she has to take care of her daughter right now, so she'll be back
I don't know, yeah, Shawna
Okay, so the cigarettes are okay, they'll be
It's got one of these harder limonades.
One's ice cold.
It's really weird earlier.
My cats all went out.
Front meowing.
The three of them, Lola, Lenore.
Tricks were all outside meowing and the dog was barking over there, and there it's going nuts. That's like, I know what's wrong
Kind of like, is that an omen or something?
Hmm, that's everyone's so quiet
I don't know. I hope it seems like
I hope my algorithm's okay. I know I've constantly been attacked
It looks like one person's here, but it's a one or 11. Oh 14. Okay, 11
Algorithm it's not messed up because people keep trying to like and we're bomb poor and bomb
You know get late, you know, so I think people are just like constantly trying to
Misses my channel, but
I'm still here
Ever this means it's you know, I just like hopefully the algorithm's okay. Oh
But maybe, you know, I'm cool with beta and cool with the say a man
You know, it's your big pipes now the pipes unfortunately was
It would probably
Had to I look different how do I look anybody here?
I'll put some cards for the chat
This I guess is for the this is for all of us. Okay, let's do three cards
Oh
King of swords energy hate flirty diamonds. We got this king of swords energy
Lion King King of swords. Oh look my nails are okay today. It's not a bath actually
King of Swords may be a Gemini Libra, you know an Aeroscient Aquarius. King of Swords, he's
really good at, you know, he has that, he can really good at cutting things off, really
intelligent, really good communicator.
Are you this king? Do you know this king?
Says scar prides himself in getting the lion's share of the brains and the family
Likewise, the king of swords is a methodical calculating leader who never that's personal feelings get in the way of his goals
This tarot card advises you to reign in your emotions and let logic guide you. Yep
Yeah, so it's like, you know, I always that sounds really
Really, I really resonate with that because sometimes we get in our emotions and when we're emotional
Sometimes we can be irrational sometimes
You know
It just makes us
Think in a non-logical way. We get all our feelings about things. You look at things logically like a little bit cold to detach sometimes
You can make some decisions without regret.
Okay.
No.
Page of Coins.
Hyenas.
Page of Coins. That's somebody, a younger person, bringing an offer.
Are you making an offer to a younger person?
Let's see.
Page of Coins indicates you're making headway toward a goal.
Whether you're looking for a new house or apartment, changing careers, starting a professional
project or helping SCAR expand its territory beyond the elephant graveyard, the page of
coins is a positive sign.
The new venture is potential to be prepared.
Yeah, it could be like a new venture or a younger person.
But it's funny because we got scar and then we got the hyenas. Okay, are we not a Lion King themed reading tonight?
Oh, oh, we have guest on we have a night. Who's this night?
Does anybody there is or that's gonna mr. Big Pipes a little bit kind of reminds me of mr. Big Pipes a little bit
but kind of arrogant and
moody
So we have night of cups
Yeah, it's watch out for these nights, you know these nights can
Be trouble, you know
Okay, night of cups night of cups represents someone charming handsome and strong like Gaston, right?
The tarot card symbolizes the ideal suitor, ready to sweep you up for feet.
It is time to strike up the band and celebrate.
Or are you longing for something else?
This tarot card advises you to follow your heart.
Hi, tacos?
For the devil likes the tacos?
Oh, I can read this one, the Ursula, the Queen of Cups.
We got the King and Queen and Queen of Cups, or how long we got the King of Swords?
There's the Queen of Cups, wow. We're in cancer right now. This is like, you know, Queen of Cups could be a cancer, you know
Like a cousin of Ursula, right? The crab, she's the octopus. You know, it's Queen of Cups. She has a really her emotions under control
And so she's really can make these calculating decisions too like Ursula, right?
But she her heart her heart will belong to the ocean, right?
The Queen of Cups
A fearsome sea witch, Ursula connects Cacock's powerful potions to manifest the desires of
those who go to her for help, but they'd better pay the price, the queen of cups represents
an intuitive, compassionate person who's always willing to help any poor, unfortunate soul
that comes her way.
Let's do one more card.
I don't know.
Anyone wants to come tonight?
Oh my gosh.
And then we got, look, we got plots of the jets of guys, we're having like some, we have any themes. There's some themes tonight plots of the jets and that's a temperance, you know, state balance.
This is very much like the two of pentacles, a very part of a balance and it looks like Pisces too, but temperance I think is more, more associated with Sagittarius.
Let's see.
It says, Ursula's beloved moray eels, flotsam and jetsam, are perfectly synchronized and
imbalanced with each other.
The tarot card temperance represents
Some sort of
Presents that same sort of flow harmony equilibrium when temperance is drawn in a terror reading its advice
Is to say fluid calm and adaptable going with the flow will make from smooth sailing even in stormy seas
Navigate any challenges that arise with calm level head in this
Temperance reminds you how important it is to maintain inner peace be careful not to be led
to let outside influences rock your boat isn't that isn't that true that there'll be like
sometimes they're flying monkeys sometimes there these you know there's more more eight
eels right these more eight eels will come you know come bothering you
um you know how they try to rock the boat and they try to like you know try to get her to
You know not kiss Eric. It's the same thing with like you know people trying to sabotage you in your in your life
You know sent by the person they you know
So first of all it was trying to breach your contract right she's trying I think that's that would be a breach of contract
For no one void so oh Erin meow
Hear me alley the nor
Yeah
It's pretty quiet today
I'm seeing you another card
The anybody like the cards just watching oh ace of coins new opportunity
The seed a new offer
Coins dropping in his hands
So it's very quiet, huh gonna need some sage saves it saves this bitch
Hey, Chris Prisma
No, that make up. Did you want to come up? Hold on, maybe it's supposed to be made in a column.
Are you gonna come up?
Hey, low key flow key. Thank you for saying that. Hey, look here like flirty diamond and flow key are members
Hey guys, hey members Doug is a member. Let's see so many members. So nice warmth my heart. I
Want to thank, you know
our you know, we had some
10-minute memberships donated in the past couple days and I
donated five
so
Kind of the family growing the angels. I'm gonna get those emojis. I promise I promise
Yeah, it's just been no little hectic
Thank you J dog. Yeah had a nice bath. It was a very nice calming bath feel a lot better
taking a bath you know it's always like you know you wash you wash yourself in
the bath and then it all goes down the drain you know all the other negativity
all the all your pasts all the you come out a new person it's kind of like
coming out of the womb in a metaphorical way and you can like you know I like
being clean also I have this you know my friend Shana is coming over gonna help
Couldn't have some more shoots. She's like she brought a vacuum and a bunch of cleaning supplies and
Really nice to have friends looking out for me
Now I know we can like sometimes tease each other and get each other's nerves
But you know, we really could really do love each other and care about the other person
I want the best for ourselves and what all of us to do the best for ourselves
Oh, yeah, fix my screen. That's a lot better
Yeah, sometimes you just get caught up in like cycles of fear and you know, depression and
confusion
It's like people you have friends to keep you grounded. I love you guys. You're so so
understanding, forgiving, accepting.
I don't want the best for self before working help.
Yep.
And now it's like, yeah, you know,
love yourself and then
Give me your potential of other people but a lot of us, you know, a lot of us have our own
Issues of self-love
So we can attract some negative lessons some hard lessons, you know, but
Basically, I believe in forgiveness
Hey tricks, what's wrong your tricks?
Yeah, so anyone want a card you're free readings tonight
Hi
I'll do a few cards for free. I'm happy too. Especially for members, I'll do like five cards.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, if we're gonna help you out.
I do want the best for myself,
I want the best for others.
So, you know, like sometimes we,
what do we sabotage ourselves sometimes?
Why do we like,
sometimes we just stop paying attention to them
and sometimes,
you gotta like, remember.
We're all we got.
No matter what, we'll be here for a second.
You know what, I woke up and guess what I saw.
There was a huge rat.
I put it in a bag and threw it out in the dark for the garbage, but
Slow key. Thank you. Thank you guys. It's for supporting the channel. I think you're here coming by stopping say
I know I'm on a lot, you know, sometimes we're more crowded than others, you know, I'm here to give a plethora
No
You know, you know weirdo
Hey
Maybe
It's just some who-do cars
These are interesting because hooters are also pretty, pretty simple.
It's usually stuff you have in your household or simple, you know, vegetables or...
Hi guys! Doing some readings.
Okay, let's do some... oops, starts from here.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you, man. Thank you, man. Okay. Thank you.
We just son of baskets. Okay, this is like a page of pinnacles
Get the baskets like basket full of something
Baskets, I think a pinnacle son back
of baskets. It says son of baskets. Okay. 89. It says, what cat is that? Yeah, that's
Plant Maypop. This is the son of baskets is depicted as a little boy collecting Maypop flowers near Cumberland Falls in Kentucky
Called the Niagara of the South. Cumberland Falls was considered sacred by many Native Americans
Moonbows, a rainbow produced by moonlight instead of sunlight, which are rare are common at Cumberland Falls
It is said that flowers and herbs collected the day after a moonbow are much more potent and were sought after by local root workers
meaning
The son of Baskis is the archetype of the idealist. On the positive side, he's artistic,
deep, inquisitive, unafraid of intimacy or commitment, and has the ability to see the
big picture with the great sense of humor. On the negative side, he's immature, unproductive,
undiscerning, a voice responsibility, and it's completely detached from reality, a loafer,
or just plain dumb. In this reading, if he doesn't represent a literal person with these
What the where the fuck KMC been I don't know hey Jenny girl. Yeah, that's tricks. How are you guys doing?
Are you doing tricks? Where are you? Oh?
Yep, I can relate to that I
Can be I can be those things sometimes, you know, but just sometimes sometimes we can all have these negative
Getting bad qualities roll roll a lot of things
We look at this one the daughter of knives
He's not happy. Sure x come on. This is a daughter of knives
There what's happening there it's kind of creepy one because they've got these arms reaching at her
The daughter of knives
As a daughter of Nives, the daughter of Nives is a spiritualist who has made contact with
the plethora of spirits via her talking board.
She's talented at what she does, so it's messages that come so fast, it's almost overwhelming.
It says, meaning, the daughter of nines represents swift delivery of messages and the accomplishment
of goals.
On the positive side, she's logical, quick-witted, action-oriented, well-informed, direct, philosophical,
and always up for a challenge.
On the negative side, she is sarcastic, condescending, rude, impatient, domineering, insensitive,
acidic, and pedantic.
In her reading, if she doesn't represent a literal person, there are these qualities
Sounds like asmr with cards. You like it
Well, if anyone wins the card for themselves, I got a card for you. I'll put one more car from this food deck. Oh
Eight of knives. Okay, a crossroad guys where this crossroads right here
Nightbot grab your balls nightbot. No touching the men. I
Don't want any problems
Or oh, but I'm touching the women don't touching the women either, but I think my part my thoughts gay. It's relaxing
Okay, we got this eight of knives. This is a crossword right there
We're in this crossword. Do we all tell me I'll come to you know the eight of knives like eight of swords
So we're also kind of we're just standing in that crossword thinking like everything's blocked
You can walk between the swords. Just don't you know?
Eight of knives, okay
Meow meow meow
This plant star anise
The image a man stands in the middle of the crossroads with two knives stuck in the ground at the entrance of each pathway
Crossroads are considered powerful places where physical and spiritual worlds meet
meaning
positive believing in yourself
Again, empowered thinking, the removal of obstacles,
escape from bondage, acquittal, being productive,
a much needed release, ceasing to be your own worst enemy,
liberating oneself from victim mentality, renewed hope,
finding a way out of predicament.
That's the positive side.
I like to think of the positive
because it's kind of a negative card.
And so let's go with the positive meaning for the card, okay?
Let's say we're getting out of these things, right?
Just think of the opposite of those the things that were the states we are before coming out of it
You know, let's go cross again to like a better state, right?
so
Let's do it together
Everyone's been doing good, so I have this I do have a
Where's my it later? Hey, you're coming over they're coming over, huh?
Say hi, okay, it's okay
No, it's attention, okay
Let's do like we can oh here. I hear Lenore to
Lenore
I got some sage.
Let's burn away.
So much of the things that we worry about.
He said to bless your home with prayer and cleansing. Yes, I said a psalm
It's Psalm 38. I'll do another psalm, too
Burn this bless and bless this house
Okay, we all negative energy all negative thought forms
All the way out to the door, yeah
I took a nice spiritual bath, too. Hey, babe, get a nice spiritual bath
clears out the... Sage is very effective, you know. It smells beautiful too. But one
time I put some sage in the freezer. One person does? It takes away all the people?
Eleven? Okay. I don't know if I'm always seeing double, right?
Beautiful, huh? Okay. Yeah
So how's everyone doing?
Yeah, it's been pretty quiet here lately. I'm sorry, you know
you guys help out I don't know by like
Sharing the channel live or I was leaving sorry
Maybe I have it. Maybe I have the curse
Bible verses see
Pick a number
God is our refuge and strength and ever presents help and trouble.
Therefore we will not fear though the earth give way and the mountains fall into the heart of the
sea, though its waters roared foam and the mountains quake with their surging.
There is a river whose streams make glad the city of God.
The holy place where the Most High dwells.
God is within her, she will not fall.
God will help her at break of day.
Nations are an uproar, kingdoms fall.
He lists his voice, the earth melts.
The Lord Almighty is with us, the God of Jacob is our fortress.
Come and see what the Lord has done, the desolation he has brought to the earth.
He makes waste worsties to the ends of the earth. He breaks the bow and shatters the spear
He burns the shields with fire. He says be still and know that I am God. I will be exalted among the nations
I will be exalted in the earth
The Lord Almighty is with us the God of the God Jacob is our fortress
Yeah, even keep an agenda on free TV news. I know I ran. Okay. There's some developments. Yeah, I know it's you know
I'm yeah, I
Don't I'm not really been following. I'm just you know
Hopefully I just you know pray for everybody and you know, if everything is okay with that, you know, I
I'm sure there's a lot of tension right now with a lot of people I kind of play I've kind of been playing out on YouTube
How have you guys been doing?
Pretty good mood. I'm just gonna have some alcohol and I
Couldn't link. I didn't do the link. I'll put the link
I guess I'll read.
Okay
So
This is from the devil's picture book. I'll probably read the whole book
Says whether you know it or not i'll read it over time not all the day
So whether you know it or not each time you pick up a deck of playing cards
You're putting your soul in immediate danger of hellfire
So, the church once said, the tarot was a medieval prototype for our present-day deck.
Instead of hearts, diamonds, spades, and clubs, it also used cups, coins, swords, and batons
as symbols.
In addition, it also contained a series of 22 mysterious picture cards called trumps.
This was their true danger.
Worse yet, within the cards lurked devils disguised as kings and heroes.
To quote a 17th century moralist on this point.
Hey, reality Nancy.
The play of cards is an invention of the devil,
which he found out that he might be easier to bring idolatry amongst men.
For the king and court cards that we use now, or once in old times,
the images of idols of false gods, which since
They, that would seem Christian, have changed into Charlemagne, Lancelot, Hector, and such
like things, because they would not seem to imitate their idolatry therein, and yet maintain
the play itself.
So this indicates a connection between playing cards and witchcraft.
The witches' practice, drawn from old pagan cults, is becoming more and more a matter
of common knowledge.
The remnants of these old cults have boldly remained on display, for all to see down the
ages is not well known.
Hi, hi Nancy anthropologists generally recognize two fruitful places to search for paying your remnants
Okay, then we're waiting for this and things what we can see
But we can read more later I mean there's a lot to it
It's not it tells all it's a really good book is from the 70s. I think
How are you, Nancy?
How has the entire thing been going?
Love you, Nancy.
So how's everyone doing?
Pretty quiet today.
It's 6.41 PM.
Are there people on?
Wish people would talk to me.
A lot of just sick.
Okay, hi
Everyone seemed good yeah, yeah
So Bita was here this morning. She's um, you know, she hadn't had a bite with 30 diamond a little bit
in the chat
You know, I
Think she's like now. She's I think she's really hurt. Do I think you congratulate raging demon. He came out. Hold on
Did he come out of the closet? Tell me about it?
Did he I heard he said he would mean I know he like
I'm talking of flirty diamond for a long time, right? Oh shit, but did he
Yeah, he's okay to have peace
Flirty him or dating man. Oh my gosh flirty are you here?
Floor do you come up? They're e-dating
Well, well, I don't know we're aging even came in very rude this morning. It's a very rude thing. It's a beta and me
but mostly beta and
Yeah, I like peace and quiet right you know
Was she nice or
She was like, oh, well, she's like, oh, no, like, you know, sake, you know, sake he doesn't like
All I care is about his attention. All the man's bunch after you have modded them. They only came here from being a mod
Yeah, isn't that crazy some people probably did but it's like, you know, I mean if you want to be a mod that bad
I mean, you know, I don't really
Yeah, I was just having so many problems with mods
You know, but if you want if you really want to be a mod like
You know, I have you have like probably two spaces available
But I have to have known you for a long time like
Like Nancy
That's not so bad, you know, but you know the most times will be a
Yeah
Yeah, so she was so she was like, you know, I was like in the shade no one checks up on me and she's like
But then she you know, she said she was nice, but I know she's free for like 12 hours last night and she's up
Bye. I don't know
I'm very good at the social stuff
Never care about my status too much too much too much work. Yeah
Yeah, well, it's especially my chat it was like
Really didn't it's like the mods were like just people were always like say oh my god
They're coming people have a public podcast
You want to come up on piano come up on panel come say hi to me
People have complained a lot about mods or the mods people were asking for wrenches people were
you know
so
It's pretty cat. Yeah, it's a tricks
Yeah, it's like sometimes I just have so many comments coming and it's like and then you know
I do have I do have a silent mod, you know that can delete stuff but
You know some sense comments are mean and so
You haven't gone to live, you haven't gone live in almost two months, for some reasons
due to X. I'm sorry, X in cancer, I'm sorry. Well yeah, you do when you feel it. But I
think like, you know, it'd be good, you know, to say hi to your people and I think David
Okay, I'm sorry it sounds no
Hope everything's okay feeling better
Thanks everyone coming in I see a lot of people coming in
It's for dinner tonight
Am I gonna go on the bike run? Well, I have a silver's pasta from last night
And coffee, I have some drinks
Probably be quite an I don't think I'll get any more food
I love ordering food. It's the thing
So
My gosh
Yeah, I think I was that it was pretty good. I mean I was decent. I mean I want to heat it up
but
Yeah
Gotta stress lately. I'm just stressed
I was thinking this term, let me see, I asked somebody about it. They're like, oh my god, yeah.
Why? Why what?
It says, earworms, also known as stuck-song syndrome or musical itch, are the experience
of having catchy songs or jingle get stuck in your head and replay involuntarily off
in a loop.
These stifling music can be annoying and distracting, but they are generally harmless
and very common, without the 98 people experiencing them.
What causes them?
Repetition.
Earworms are triggered by hearing a song multiple times or by a song's repetitive nature.
Your stress?
I'm sorry.
Recent exposures, the most recent song of her is more likely to get stuck.
Emotional triggers, emotions, associations, and even stress can trigger earworms.
Auditory cortex gaps, these can be triggered by gaps in the auditory cortex of the brain.
Catchy tunes, songs with strong, memorable melodies and rhythms are more prone to becoming
an earworm.
So it's the same it's like music here, but it's like I'd say
No, you said you're stressed. Oh, you're why am I stressed? Yeah. Well, you know, it's uh, I mean
My channel's kind of an under attack like either like few days ago. I was just getting form bomb constantly
Yeah, I love people mad at me for like, you know
Pretty much no reason but I I don't know
Maybe I'm not the perfect that goes perfect. You know, I know I know I've like, you know, let a lot of drama happen
Hi tree frog. Good to see you
Let a lot of drama happen in this show, you know
Really
Some people got mad about it
Thank you
But I really do want people to like, you know work things out get along like I like resolution and stuff like that
So it's sometimes it's constantly. Yeah, I feel like I feel it'll be okay. You know
I'm sorry about it's really about a tarot card
Am I hungry? Oh, I'm not too hungry
So this is about this is called the juggler the juggler is actually the the magician
It says, entitled in Modern Dex, The Magician or the Magus, this card originally showed a
fairground huckster.
What the fuck?
He found out Sweden is dating Flirty Diamond.
Really?
Flirty Diamond, tell me about this.
The card originally showed a fairground huckster in the process of either selling trinkets
or performing a sleight of hand trick.
Alternatively, in some cards, he's telling a fortune.
You have if I was am I hungry? Oh, thank you so much
You know, I'm a subway
So sweet you're gonna you always have I love I love you to do a reading for you if you'd like a reading
Hey, Charlie. Oh
She ate his ass. Oh my god, how can she do that like a reading? Okay?
I like to go subway has a
Has this a these are
Daily specials the mic over there later
You can see he has the mess and sought messages psyche raging toss. Oh my gosh. There's messages. Oh my gosh
Hi Charlie
So for Jenny, okay, Jenny you got this king of cups a king of cups. That's captain. It's captain hook, you know
The captain hooks you see, you know, he's a little bit my this guy might drink I think it's like eight bucks
She fuck has been sometime so it is oh, yeah
So but this king of cups. Okay, this king cups, you know, well cups are water. So this guy, you know
he's pretty much a control of his emotions, but
He's living growing up, but you know, he is an emotional man
Okay about this it's interesting if you captain hook for this one helps because you know
King of Cups is usually pretty compassionate
But so it says the King of Cups is a charming caring and kind
Leader with strong moral code the tarot card advises you to stay true to yourself and keep your emotions in check
lashing out at others
As ill-tempered captain hook would won't benefit you and outbursts will only attract the attention of the dreaded crocodile
Stay calm, compassionate and collected
I'll put on the banner up. Thank you so much
It's right there, thank you so much
The king of cubs. Yes, uh, yeah, well depends on the king of cubs, but
But yeah, like if he's compassionate and he's calm cool, he's just in control of his emotions. Okay, next
You have this justice card
So this justice card telling me that
Things are coming things are coming into balance for you. They're made me fair. You're getting some justice about something
You know says
When brilliant, well-rounded scientist Dr. Caligan suffers a personal tragedy, he embraces
a new secret identity as the masked yokai to seek vengeance.
Just as revenge-motivated yokai struggles with the morality of his action, the tarot
card justice represents repercussions, consequences, ethics, and fairness.
Have you been feeling morally conflicted about a situation in your life?
Are you in a situation or relationship that doesn't feel right to you?
The tarot card justice advises you to follow your moral compass regardless of your personal feelings in the matter
It's a clear sign that now is the time to stand boldly for truth and integrity
It may be hard, but it will lead to peace and stability in the long run
Thank you, he man. Thank you so much. So you're giving justice for something maybe that king of cups will help you or
you know
Okay, what do we got next?
Okay, the world, but you're getting this justice will become completion of a cycle.
And so this is a very good thing, this world card, cycle completion successfully.
The world, that's completion, transformation, and achieving goals that have long been worked
is able to summon the Cauldron board.
Says you're at the end of a long arduous journey
and success is at hand.
Savor the moment by reflecting everything
it took for you to get here.
You've worked hard and are finally achieving
your long-term goals.
Pause to enjoy your success.
You are stepping into the next phase of your life.
The world calls for a celebration.
Is this the white photo?
Has like the it should have like the eight, you know, so keep it in psyche on it. I think
Yeah, I think it says yes, it says it has like the angels on it
So they could send like streaming inside beautiful home. Okay
What else we got for you? Oh
two of wands. Oh shit
No, like I came up with another card two of wands before you got the captain hook card this four cups
And then there's two of wands, you're coming together with somebody.
And there's going to be some offers made to you and you're going to want to make sure
that, you know, you might reject the first few, but wait for the right one, wait for
the right one.
You don't have to accept all the offers.
There's the right one for you.
Then putting your energy together with someone else.
Thank you so much.
I'll just show you my cards for you. Ace of Cups, this is going to be a new Love Offers,
it's going to be coming in for you. Ace of Cups, or Jewish Cheers, some kind of
romantic thing, and then we have this King of Wands too, so I don't know if this Love Offers
is coming from this King of Wands. Okay, thank you so much. This King of Wands, he's a very passionate
guy, but in control of his passions, they have Jafar there.
It looks like ever it looks like after the news after the completion of the cycle there's gonna be
To the new opportunity in love, but it looks like you're coming out of the cycle. Oh
Thank you so much. Oh, oh my god. Thank you so much. I
Appreciate you so much
Hey, and let let me know if you want more cards one second. Okay
How are we doing buddy? We got the old uh Disney Charo cards out? Yeah doing some readings
Doing some readings doing having a nice night. How are you doing? What the heck is that?
That pirate from that was on the one card is that little mermaid or what the pirate from from a captain hook
That's that's from Peter Pan. I'll be damned. I'll be damned. It's been so long. I
Was born in 88. I grew up in the 90s. We had all those
We had all those Disney movies growing up on VHS. Oh, we got somebody else here. Hello. Hello Trevor
Hi, nice to meet you.
Hello, psych.
Hi, hi, Dougie, this is Trevor, he's a friend of mine.
Trevor's a big guy, yep.
Nice to meet you.
How was your night, Dougie?
How's my night?
Yeah, I'm in my attic,
because it's the only room in my house I can smoke in,
and it's 86 degrees outside, it was 98 today.
My attic's like an oven.
Are you in the Midwest?
No sir, I'm in New York.
Oh you're in New York, okay.
I'm not in the city, I'm about 15 miles from New York City.
Oh I got you, okay.
I'm near the city, you know.
Where'd you move from?
I was born. We lived in the city when I was born. We moved out when I was like two and a half years old
I don't have any recollection of living in New York City. Oh, I got you. Okay. So we moved up to the suburbs and here
I've been raised in what the school?
Okay, very nice very nice
What about you Trevor, where are you from?
I am in the beautiful city, some might say the Mecca, the Mecca of the Midwest, Grand Rapids, Michigan.
Grand Rapids, Michigan, okay.
I'm not sure if you're familiar with old, old Jerry Ford, Gerald R. Ford, that is.
Gerald R. Ford, yep.
Quite famous for tripping, falling over, yeah.
Oh
Gerald Ford I think famously tripped and fell didn't he quite famously maybe maybe not
Maybe that was just chubby chase pretending
It was Gerald Ford Gerald Ford cuz he was like the football player at one time and then he was like walk up there
Yeah, exactly. Yeah. Yeah, he had some famous falls
I always bring up Gerald Ford jokingly.
That's our claim to fame here in Grand Rapids, Michigan.
Gerald Ford was the native here.
So I bring that up jokingly.
But yeah, what's the topic of conversation?
Me and Doug, you wanna know,
what's the topic of conversation tonight, Syke?
No, I don't. I don't. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk to you. I don't want to talk
Just maybe
There you go, I fixed it. I fixed it. Yep. There you go. That's better
Don't you can hear me, sir. I hear you better now. Yes. Oh nice. Thank goodness
Thank goodness. Do you have cats, Dougie? Because sightcams a lot of cats. Are you a?
Are you a cat? Oh, there's the tabby
I've had cats my whole life, but lately we've had dogs
Dogs Jenny. Thank you so much. Jenny. I love you. All right. Yeah
Jenny girl Jen Jen see you later
Jenny, thank you so much for buying the reading. Thank you so much
Are you into the doggie? Are you into the tarot cards? Not particularly. No
Um, I came across psych because I don't know if you're aware, but psych made a huge splash in another chat community just recently
And everybody on all the chats was talking about it
Right, that's basically how I heard I met I would say
Maybe a couple of weeks ago, right? Mm-hmm. So what were they saying Dougie? What were they saying about me?
Good and bad. You know how it is in chat, right? Sorry. Yeah
They're falling to take over your chat, but you know, I don't need to go into that. Yeah, okay
Yeah, buddy by name, but of course they're all talking about, you know, you know, they're gonna come and take over
Yeah
It's all crap. Yeah
Um, you know, I hang in some pretty miserable chat communities. I also hang out with some very cool chat communities
You know, it's all over the place
Yeah
Dugdee is some fool who tries to pretend to be me. That's who's done. Yeah
Before you speak too much, I'm not sure he's a fool
except that his actions when he
Uses the name and he put my picture in his avatar like my picture of me
Okay, that I think that's foolish behavior
Yeah
Not only that if you go on Dougie's channel and you read underneath where the where the app email is
It's Dougie Doug. It says Dougie Doug
No, yeah
Whatever it was this if someone calls you and they actually use your name and your picture
You can go on their channel and report them and YouTube will do something about it
But if they change one letter or if they use your name, but not your avatar then YouTube doesn't do nothing about it
you know
But if they call you if they call you exactly and use your same avatar and your same name and you report them
YouTube will not the channel down
Yeah, well, I I have a parody Elon Musk account and then I have a parody Nicholas Cage account
You know, I guess but I think the picture. Yeah
I used to go to, yeah, I used to go to M.S.
We're the same birthday, you know,
Jake Cage and I were born on the same birthday.
But, yeah.
Did you see that Daddy Long Legs movie
that everybody said he's so great in?
The, I've seen scenes, I've seen clips,
I haven't seen the whole movie.
But everybody said he was like really good in it.
The, some more movie, Daddy, Daddy Long Legs.
I didn't see it, I didn't see it.
But he's weird.
Yeah, you know what, you know what?
and
God, I can't, the Omen or some classic horror movie, it was uh...
The Omen was a great movie. Uh, well, I mean, it is day. I guess now it's dated, but yeah.
This particular movie came out, uh, this is what I remember about it. I went to go see it with my friends.
The last movie I've seen in theaters, it was June 6th.
2006. That was the big thing. 666. Yeah. And it was a remake of some movie. I think it was
maybe the Omen. I don't even remember it's been so long. Some remake of some movie. It wasn't great.
It was not great at all. It was pretty bad. It's gotta go. Look at that. Yeah, yeah.
Well, Charlie you mistaken because Doug D someone different
That's the problem people people people easily believe anybody
In YouTube right everything you hear is not true, but people choose to believe everything they hear anyway, right? Yeah
now
You can say I was saying the other day when people come up
And they tell you negative things about a third party 95% of the time 99% they're lying
They're trying to they're trying to shade your opinion of somebody and they're pushing their own agenda
Yeah, would that fiasco the other day on the panel? I would say that that goes both ways, right in both instances
I think both people were grossly exaggerating the truth telling you negative things about the other one, right? Yeah
Now and it's not like I take sides because I don't I don't care. I'm friends with everybody if they don't want to be my friend
That's fine. I don't give a shit, right? But uh, you know, I don't I don't ever make disparaging remarks about anyone
But I will be honest
Okay, Odessa, thank you
But but that's my daughter coming home
But I will be honest, you know what I mean, and if I think someone is
like
You know trying to influence your opinion of people in an unfair manner
Fuck I'll call that out. You know what I mean
Yeah
Thank you, you know, it's like cuz I have a lot of people telling me a lot of things and I do like you know
I do like trying to have my own opinion of people and like his people are telling me
Oh band this person this person this person this this person is something bad this person something bad
I can't research everybody
Make your own this is my policy in YouTube. I don't accept anybody else's opinion about someone
I want to meet the person talk to them and I'll form my own opinion
Someone's gonna tell me oh, this guy did this. Oh, and he did that. He said this. He said I don't give a fuck
Yeah, I really don't yeah heard it or saw it. I frankly I don't believe it because you know, I think it's
I think it's the person trying to push their own agenda
Yeah
But
Yeah, it's really quick. Uh, I know I left everybody like just hanging on the ledge there in regards to the last
I've seen
January 6 2006. It was indeed the remake of the omen. I just looked it up
Okay, I just wanted to let everybody know I I know everybody was real curious about that, but
Go ahead Dougie if you would if you would
The drama community I guess what are we talking about?
Yeah, well some community he's here saying he doesn't believe anything here
Yeah, well you have to be careful with this people yeah people do have their own judges
I was constantly or constantly trying to break me up with any friends of mine that constantly try into like
Attack, you know people that supported the channel and so
You know, I try to like that's why you know, I keep I keep pretty much
yeah, don't donations or things like that anonymous and things and
because
People are so interested in like my donations. They're like, oh my gosh. He's getting there
They talk about other channels like you know, so it's like, you know, it's really and
They're worried about you know, I don't know the vibe is concerned so concerned about me. It's like
the
So that's what I'm saying. Just ignore all this shit everybody says
Form your own opinions about people
Yeah
Well, I think I'm gonna I think I'm gonna draw a picture of Dougie Doug
I'm gonna draw your picture because I've been drawing pictures of people in your mind
I'll draw your picture Dougie. I don't mind if you draw a picture of me
Okay, I hope it's good. I'm better looking in the picture than I am in real life
I feel like I'm gonna hold are you sir? If you don't mind me asking. I am 36. I mean
I'll just say this. I have a son who's 35. Oh
Really? Okay. Okay. Gotcha. Gotcha
Sikes like 25 26
How are you again psych in your 20s, right? I'm uh, I'm actually like a 44. Oh
I'll be Dan's
What are you doing psych what are you I'm trying a picture of a I'm trying a picture of a
I do oh you do
in the illustrator. In the illustrator, if you will.
But all right, friends. All right.
Okay, Dougie. Thank you.
Dougie, it was nice to meet you, sir.
Trevor, you're losing.
Yeah, yeah, usually just stay on for a minute,
stay high to psych, make some conversation, and,
and yeah.
I don't really have much to say. I just basically go see my wife.
I will say this, Trevor, although I don't know you at all except to say hello just now.
You look very trepidatious in your avatar there.
Yeah, it sounds about right, Dougie.
Yeah, it sounds about right, sir.
All right, well, all right, I'll leave you two to it.
I can't wait to see this picture that Psych is drawing.
I'll be watching from the chat.
So good to talk to everybody, all right, bye.
Thanks, Trevor, you're awesome.
Okay, Doug, I almost got it.
I hope I hope you don't mind. No worries. Take your time. It's like not the best. I mean
Sometimes I'm better than other times. Mm-hmm. You ready to see how?
I need to fill the hair a little bit. You got a nice hair
Okay, there we go
Okay, right
Okay, Dougie Doug, I don't frankly don't see much resemblance, but you know
Okay, I'll tell you what though you're about as good an artist as I am
Right, I could I think I could draw that wall. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah
Okay, well, yeah, I mean, I don't if you see I don't know if you know if you see my picture of Gotti
I do a picture of Gotti
Did you a picture of God? Yeah
Did you include the goiter the softball size goiter? I
Look, I put a band-aid on his head. Oh, there you go
Yeah, that looks right
There's a donut in a banana. I thought I was trying to let's tell that that's what I hear of course
I've never nobody's ever seen God he got he has never shown himself ever on a panel to my knowledge
He reminds me of that villain in a Inspector Gadget.
He had the cat, but you never saw his face.
Yeah, yeah.
And to my knowledge, I've never had anyone
tell me they've seen Gotti in a backstage or anything
like that.
As far as I know, Gotti could look like anything, right?
And not that I even care, but I I've heard people speculate about his appearance
One thing that's commonly speculated is a is a goiter, but I don't know once again
I don't know that there's any truth to that whatsoever
You know, I kind of imagine him like Phantom of the Opera. Like, you know the Phantom of the Opera
It was like a mask
He once told me that he's confined to a wheelchair again. I don't know if he's fucking with me or being straight up
I have no way of knowing, you know
But who knows
Yeah, well I
I don't know. He's been kind to me for the most part, you know
like
He's a little rough around the edges, but
Magani
You know, he's, he's, you know, he's basically people ignore him. Right. So that's so good. Right. Because he don't have nothing much to say.
I believe that he's like everybody like everybody in the chat capable of being perfectly decent when they want to.
And that they go into chat.
And they, you know, they default to their childhood or something, you know what I mean?
And it's like, yeah.
Some people are really into playing, you know, they're really into playing the character.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it's like a total role play and, you know, I don't, you know, I never know how
much, because basically they can say anything for somebody that's an improv or like, you
know, an actor.
Who'd like to try different characters, you know, it's a it's a you can go you can go to this
You can go to a chat or a panel you go to and you can go into a different voice a different character
It's even fool everybody and you know test yourself and you know entertain people
He came on my panel about two weeks ago, maybe three weeks ago
And until I left your panel the other day, I didn't realize it.
He came on wearing the same wig.
He was a little less shaven though.
He had a little more facial hair when he came up and saw me.
And I asked him, I said, who are you? Where are you from?
He said, I don't know what he said.
And I said, why are you wearing a wig?
And he got defensive about the wig.
And then he started acting funny, shifting and like moving and like looking.
And so I threw him off the panel.
I was afraid he was getting ready to do something that I wouldn't want him doing, you know what I mean?
Yeah, but, yeah.
I remember, because I was on the panel with him, was it yesterday or this morning? I think it was yesterday, right?
Yeah.
And I realized after I got off, this guy's been on my fucking panel. Yeah.
Yeah, well, he's a character like, you know, and it's like, you know, I don't know why the wig
I don't know why you know if he thinks he's that recognizable, you know, but uh, or
He really just isn't this character doesn't want his face shown and you know very mysterious
He's funny, but it's like it's just like you can't get a straight. It's like when people can't be serious
I mean unless there's some people you know if they know that's why he's like he's a character
I mean it's like something but it's funny to like interview like a non-serious person, but it's kind of like
Unless they have some good material. It's not that funny after
Seiki is trying to put a positive vibe going to but Dougie's assist on talking to people who aren't you know
I know he's not talking to people that are in here
It was a chat talking about people yeah, and I got to clarify something for Hannah
Right. Yeah, people are not everybody who knows them. I think smart people ignore
Hannah is what I'm gonna. Let me just clarify that
Right smart people ignore
Yeah, I mean it's like and I have to start you know ignoring some people like because some people were artists like
Here hurt my panel, you know, SIG
You know all D 5k
No, well me but you know me or they're not here
But it's like they're welcome to come and defend themselves
But you know if I mentioned somebody where people were allowed to talk about other streamers and things like that people that are
Stream their public figures in a way so you can discuss them, right?
It's like if they're like we're talking about people that are just in the chat and things like that. We're talking about streamers
so
Well, or at least he's a he's a panel verse person, right?
Yeah, so, you know, I don't know why I don't know why I missed your bagpipes and then I had I had
Ilya in a in a kilt. I think it was must have been Scottish Scottish evening or something
Which is pretty cool, but
I'm just glad he didn't lift the kill too high, but yeah, that was very lucky that you know
Why else would Dougie talk about it if food or gospel?
We don't be the cool guy. So what are you? What are you going on live again? Dougie wins your
You know, I went live yesterday, I was out on the Long Island sound fishing
We caught some straight bass. It was quite nice
But my dad probably do a panel tomorrow night. If not tomorrow the next day. I don't have a schedule
You know, yeah, but I'd like to come by and stop by your panel soon if I can catch it
Yeah, I promise I'll behave myself. I won't I'll try not to bring controversy or no
I put my porch team up every night on my porch. Mm-hmm, but that's not like I don't host it
I'm not there talking. That's just a place where people go and talk. It's like, you know what I mean?
Yep
of the
Well, good, you know, it's a you know, I sometimes I put a lot of my videos on members only
Sometimes I've had there's a lot of videos unfortunately because I'll just get you know
Porn bombed or n-word bombed and even though it's like, you know
See any n-word. I think it's probably like you're not gonna figure the
Yeah, computer, but then those people trying to flag flag my channel about it eventually. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and then yeah, you know
So I tried to
You know
But yeah, my monetization is you know, I've been monetized for over three months now
You know it has like a few few scares, but I
Think like if things are coming out of the benefit of like, you know, I can't call me down a little bit
Like I guess like, you know
Accidental saw to me. Yeah, I looked at this account already
August 30th 2023
Accidental saw to me
Yeah, I've seen him chatting under the name accidental sodomy. I guess and what I've seen
Accidental so I mean. Oh my gosh
That's that's that's the name of the channel. That's not the name of the
That's not the chat name. He's using now, but that's the account that he set up was accidental sodomy. Oh, no
He's only last chatter bait stream. Oh my god, you're there
Foodie bandit knows too much
Yeah, well
He just keeps saying it
Yeah, so but yeah, YouTube's been it's been
Going pretty well. I mean, it's like just for you and just for me six months on
Actually, I see it's June now, so I've been I've been doing I've been doing almost I thought it's your life
I've almost doing been doing lives you for almost seven months. And so wow what a journey guys. What a journey
This was my dream to do a YouTube show and I finally was at the balls to do it last year and
You know, it's just come better than I could have kind of imagined so many cool people
Yeah supportive
It can be it can be fun when it goes well
It looks like it's got a bunch of AI songs and stuff something AI something on their channel and then a rangatang look at that
I love the AI.
April 5th, 2024.
JT, do you want to come say hi to Duggy Duggy?
You know JT Duggy Duggy?
Will you use burning JT?
Yeah, a lot of times when I,
like a lot of people do lurk in the chat
and so sometimes
As soon as we bring a name up the person's right there. They're like, hey, well, what do you say?
So, you know, sometimes people sometimes just kind of summoning a person
Yeah, we have our says the new allies. Well, who's in Alex?
We your ears. Well, you know your ears people's ears berm because we meant we were mentioning your name someone
Yeah, your name was mentioned. That's all have you never heard the expression before JT?
Yeah. Oh, yeah, you see you saw JT. I do I drew JT too, of course
Yeah, I'm the picture me
Okay. Well, here's JT first. There's JT
Okay, he's got balloons. He has balloons. Yeah, he'll look one for him and one for Ray and there's Dougie Doug
Yeah. Yeah. There you go.
sketchbook with a picture of
everybody. Well, I mean, you
know, I drew a bunch of people.
I drew DJ Electra. I don't
think you did. Uh did you do
Electra? Gaudi? Road to Mad? I
drew. Uh yeah, I have a I have
a bunch of you know, you know,
easy cameras on. Easy cameras.
Easy. Yeah. So, that's that's
You know sassy scarlet? Yeah, I mean, I don't need it. I don't know these people I see their name in chat. That's all
Sassy yeah, yeah
I just see their name go by and chat your time time time who just time
He's like a dog
Yeah
The dog home we would get so long to go
Hello hello
Hello, hey, Michael. Hi. Hi. Hi. How are you? I'm doing fine. Thank you. How about yourself pretty good?
Yo, Dougie Doug, what's going on Dougie not much good good? Do I know you?
Um, I
Don't think so. No, I don't think so. Can you never challenge under a different name? Did you know? No, no, no, no
So what are we doing? What was it tarot?
Yeah, I do tarot card readings. You do tarot card. Can you can you get can you can you give me a reading?
Yeah
For real. Yeah, the museum cards. Yeah
Nice. Okay. Okay
I'm ready I'm excited. Okay, you're excited. Okay. I'm excited
Okay, hope so Michael Lanhart
Okay, you got this okay nine of pentacles. Okay, so you got a lot of abundance a lot of abundance around you
You'd like then you have a beautiful garden. You've got
You know, I don't know animals really like you animals really like you animals coming up to you
Just like things growing around you. You're like good vibes. Good vibes. Yeah. Yeah
So I would say nine of pentacles over here for me. This is nine of hedgehogs for
so it says
It says like the regal queen of hearts, you're enjoying bounty and abundance. You have all material resources
You need to feel comfortable and secure relax pamper yourself and gather friends for a game of croquet
It's time to enjoy yourself
Is that a reference to Lewis Carroll? Yeah, this is the Alice in Wonderland
Okay, then we got for you. Okay, so this is temperance. Okay, so this is temperance
This is also like an alchemy. This is like taking you know
If there's negative stuff that happens you're able to turn to pause or turn to positive
You're able to blend energies. You're able to like pick the right people to
Yeah, the right group to party with you were able but also
You know, it's about you know, not partying too hard not doing too too much of any one thing same balance and
Even in the even in the spiritual material where you're doing a good job of same balance right now
Wow, and then we have this ten of flowers.
Okay, so the ten of flowers is ten of ones.
So you've also been taking on a lot of responsibilities.
Maybe some burdens of other people.
You're helping other people maybe.
But, you know, just make sure that you're not hearing too many burdens.
You can always, you know, put some of the burdens down.
So true.
Take a break.
That's true?
Okay.
That's true.
That's very true.
This is on the panel.
Give me a couple more
You've got your future laid out for you. Look at that. Yo, this guy's good. Yo, this guy's good, man
Yeah, so finally, I'll just say you have this the advice is like this king of swords. It's got the rabbit king of swords
It's it's like it's a you know, just very intelligent and good communicator
I just I open right to the book to it right over the page
It says the king of spears represents a shrewd calculating person who commands respect like the March hair
He's very assertive way of communicating and not easily moved by the emotions of others the tarot card advising you to be
Clear focus confident in your interactions with people and so that's the advice for you out of that. So wow, just be very clear
but you know because your words are powerful and
And
You know, you know, so be clear with your intentions and that's it. Hey, Spunky. How are you? Hey everybody?
Thank you. Thank you for that man. Thank you. You're welcome. I hope you enjoyed the reading
You know, thank you man being polite
And who how'd you find the channel by the way? Oh
I'm sorry you it was just on like YouTube live or through the live filtered it live and yeah, you popped up
Well, if you can do me a favor to subscribe to the channel, you know and
You know tell if you share with your friends or something like that. It's nice to have you here. You're a cool guy
Thank you for being so polite
No worries, man. I worries
Cool, thank you for doing that man. Yeah, did you read Duggy? Did you read Duggy's?
Duggy like a reading? I got my Tarot card. The other day he read me some. I'm not too worried about it
If if you want to hear my Tarot, you get it. Was it right? Was it good?
I guess in some extent. I honestly don't really remember all that he said. Yeah, okay. Well, I got some free Duggy
So Duggy. Oh, hold on one second
Oh, this was sick of me Doug Dougie Queen of Cups. Okay. Are you are you married? You're not married. Are you?
Okay
Well Queen of Cups, I don't know if your wife is a water sign or something, but you know, I think she
She's not your wife has like a
Really good heart. It's very caring. I see this is a very caring woman Queen of Cups
I think this is like probably
It's a video. Well, that's that's it that takes that says a lot
I think she showed up in the reading. Let me see. It says Queen of Cups.
The Queen of T-Cups represents a maternal nurturing person much like the kind mother
oysters rather than giving strict harsh orders. She tries to guide her curious oysters with
gentle compassion. The tarot card comes as a sign to make sure you're treating others with the
Yeah, that's the lesson that she gives right, you know, it's compassion and empathy
Okay. Oh, also we got okay. So we got this aid of tea cups. Okay, so eight
So this is some kind of strength in the motion. Okay, but also it's like
The eight is like you've achieved a lot you've achieved so much of what you wanted to but you there's something more
You're there's something else. You're still waiting to achieve or wanted to see you're still going you're going out and you're like
More I want to achieve. Yeah, of course
Yeah
My journey is over. Yeah, not by any means, right?
It says it says you recently achieved a goal and you put a lot of energy
But you aren't finding it fulfilling as you expected it to be it's time for introspection
If you're unsatisfied reflect on what may be self reflection will help you discover what makes you truly happy and
content
Finance has nothing to do with it, but I did achieve a goal lately that I did put some effort into and work towards
Hello
Hello, Samantha. Hello, Gary
Hi, this is Gary. Hold on
Hi, yeah, yeah, hey Gary, how's it going?
So I'll do that. Here's it. Here's an advice card for I've an advice card for Doug and
Okay, so advice. Okay, so Doug you got this advice. It says so this is you got the devil card, okay?
So the devil card for it says temptation, okay? Maybe maybe there's some temptation you should you should be you should give it to
I like I like this for you
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, come on. Oh, come on. I
said, how much more time does
Dougie have left to live? But
you know what? I think Dougie
is going to have a nice long
life, you know, and I believe
anybody knows how much more time
they got left. Yeah. We've got
to enjoy life as it comes, you
know. Can you, uh, can you
calculate how much time I have
left to live? Gary. So, so
Gary, do you know Dougie Doug?
I don't think I remember my Gary. What brings you here, Gary?
I was looking to get my care my my tarot cards read
Okay, so Gary you like your cards read to you, right? Was that was that good?
The link sign up. I think the link is pinned Ray. Hold on. Oh, I got I got you Ray
Yeah, I got okay. I got some I got a few cards for you. Okay
Yeah, give it to me
Gary Gary needs a reading. Okay. Gary needs a reading for Gary. Gary needs a reading
Gary Queen
Gary Queen of Pentacles Queen of Hedgehogs. It's a Queen of Pentacles. I'm not sure what movies from she's this really cool-looking duck
They got really
She's glasses. She's got these eggs. Okay
Queen of Hedgehogs, okay, so I don't know. Do you have this are you have a girlfriend or a wife or I see this
There's a woman around you. Who's this woman? That's a very abundant really
Yeah, maybe your mom is I got that in my mind too like the maybe the mom, okay?
Then because it was really a mother maternal maternal card right this queen of hedgehogs the queen of heads are hedgehogs is a nurturing
Practical figure who lives a fulfilling life of abundance like the mother bird. She's a maternal protective person
Takes pride in maintaining comfortable home queen of hedgehogs advises you to stay resourceful nurturing and kind, okay?
Oh, here's Ray. Let's welcome Ray. Okay, Ray
great rainbow g from twitter ray okay oh okay so also i got this this is the
hey hey hey thanks i thanks for live hi what's up you're welcome i'm just gonna
have a quick reading for uh for a friend gary gary also this this is the page of spear so this is
like you know you know this is like who is that gay who is that gary god okay please don't interrupt
I don't know who Gary is, but you know, the pages are sometimes either like a beginning of an idea or beginning of something, you know, or they can be younger people.
You got some really weird people coming up here, Si.
It's okay. I like weird people. It says the page of spirits represents someone who's eager to do their best, though the lack of attention to detail often creates mistakes like painting white roses red instead of, or white roses instead of red ones, white ones instead of red ones.
Planting white world roses and red ones though blundering the page of spears tries his best and will always try to right his wrongs
You page it with yourself and use mistakes as learning opportunities. Isn't that true guys? It's like miss mistakes are like
Oh, you know it can be bad, but
Wait, let me just do one more card for him and you got so you got the fool card and so this over here
There's a beautiful hardship. This is Alice the cat in her lap asleep. That's a nice card. That's a nice card
Well, no, it's not the fool. It's the world. It's the world. And so she's asleep. She's waking up. Oh my god
I feel like I need to get a wedding present after after he quotes. He's
This is the world and the world is like you know the world is a completion of a cycle it says
Alice's adventures in wonderland begin to end near a rabbit hole at the base of a tree on a beautiful day
Begin and end the world represents a satisfying completion of a long journey
It says you've come to the end of an important life changing expedition
whether this refers to actual travel or more personal internal journey
You've been met with compounding challenges. What's your problem Hannah?
Hold on. We can bear with him
He's in the chat in the chat. You've been met with that compounding challenges and joyous breakthroughs
And you've learned many lessons along the way you've reached your destination and a wiser more accomplished person
Enjoy your success. There you go. That's good. That's good. Yeah
Hey summer, hey summer. Yeah, that's good. Thank you. Thank you guys. We got a nice full panel
No, I'm I'm looking in the chat. I see I'm hot mess hot mess summers down there
So yeah, you got some bad bitches some lot wizards Samantha
Hannah we got some cool chicks here. We have shout out
Hannah Hannah Hannah answers the total loser which is okay. No, no, no, she probably has a fat pussy. Mmm. Oh
my god
Well, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about the chat, let's not talk about
I just came from my tarot reading. What's wrong? What's the big deal?
Well, Gary Gary, did you are you are you Rob Reiner, huh?
What so so why so why you dress like Count Dracula?
Okay guys
I just heard peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace peace
you're looking at me maybe but you know what they did have a concentration camp
call I think it was called I forgot what it's called it was it was a
I think camp 33 and it was it was called common sense
Mm-hmm dude the Holocaust was basically just summer camp
Okay, hold on hold on rage is rage is said gassing people is common sense, okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, let's not know more of this
Germany. Nothing with Germany before 1944. I was smoking that boy. I was smoking him.
I know, I know. I don't want to talk about...
Hold on. Let me look at it. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
I don't know why but I don't know. We shouldn't be judging people. We shouldn't be judging. I don't know
What does Ray look like Ray? What do you look like?
Yes, Ray is Ray looks like Ray looks like clean it. He looks like Cleetus from Beverly Hillbillies, but he's
gorgeous
is
Yeah, or Barney five had him like Barney five a little a better looking Barney five
He's a little more sex appeal than Don knots, right? Well Don knots did pretty good on three's company. I thought oh, yeah
I like mr. Furley. Yeah, he's classic mr. Furley. Yeah
Yeah, so what do you guys think about the war in Iran in Israel? Okay?
We don't this is not this is not CNN. This is not this is not
Could you do like the tarot readings of of like the future of politics or something?
I mean, I I mean, I think they need to finish it. Then we would need to finish it
No guys, no, I don't want to talk about Israel or any stop it
We need to kill it. We need to kill them. Oh
We need to kill all the Jews kill all the Jews. Yeah
Nick Johnson good to see you
Wow